[Speaker 1] Here is good.
[Speaker 1] Okay, then. Bye.
[Speaker 2] Listen!
[Speaker 2] Enough of dating.
[Speaker 2] Let's get married.
[Speaker 1] What?
[Speaker 1] Is that how you propose to a girl?
[Speaker 1] You're so so unromantic, really!
[Speaker 1] - Stop fooling around.
[Speaker 2] - Hold on.
[Speaker 2] I'd never fool around with you, Dimple.
[Speaker 2] Hey Buddy! What's the matter?
[Speaker 2] Run along! Lollipop, scoot!
[Speaker 1] Stop the drama. So many people around, can't you see?
[Speaker 2] I can't see anything...
[Speaker 2] other than the life I want to spend with you.
[Speaker 2] You know everything about me by now.
[Speaker 2] Whatever I am.
[Speaker 2] I really love you.
[Speaker 2] Look Dimple, I'm a simple lad from Palampur.
[Speaker 2] Please say yes?
[Speaker 2] Quick, there's a stone digging into my knee!
[Speaker 1] Yes!
[Speaker 1] Yes, I'll marry you.
[Speaker 2] I knew it. I was pointlessly stressed.
[Speaker 2] You said I'm booked, right?
[Speaker 2] Thought I'll check once.