[Speaker 1] Why aren't you married?
[Speaker 2] I really want to...
[Speaker 2] ...but haven't found that spark in anyone yet.
[Speaker 2] Tell me something.
[Speaker 2] How come a pretty girl like you became a wrestler?
[Speaker 1] Why?
[Speaker 1] Do girl wrestlers have horns on their heads?
[Speaker 2] I didn't mean that.
[Speaker 2] What I'm saying is...
[Speaker 2] ...sports like wrestling have been for men in our society.
[Speaker 2]- Girls are usually...
[Speaker 1] - Usually what?
[Speaker 1] Born to be tied to a pillar,like cattle?
[Speaker 1] I started wrestling to change that idea.
[Speaker 1] You know why I fight men in the arena?
[Speaker 1] Because your society keeps...
[Speaker 1] ...women caged behind veils from birth to death.
[Speaker 1] Your society doesn't get this simple fact...
[Speaker 1] ...if you kill daughters, how will your sons find brides?
[Speaker 1] Even my father wanted a son.
[Speaker 1] He wanted him to be a wrestler.
[Speaker 1] Who was born? Me.
[Speaker 1] My mother passed away soon after I was born.
[Speaker 1] But my father, he's a caring man.
[Speaker 1] He brought me up like a son, sent me to a Delhi college.
[Speaker 1] Nurtured my dreams like his own.
[Speaker 1] I could've stayed in Delhi...
[Speaker 1] ...but I returned to my roots.
[Speaker 1] Just watch! The day I win a medal...
[Speaker 1] ...all Haryana will be known for its Aarfa.
[Speaker 1] So watch out!
[Speaker 1] Keep your manhood tucked away.
[Speaker 1] Times are changing.
[Speaker 1] Daughters are on the move.
[Speaker 1] They'll slam you down so hard, you'll have no idea what hit you.
[Speaker 1] Why are you smiling?
[Speaker 2] You remind me of Rani Laxmibai of Jhansi.
[Speaker 2] You're modern from the outside.
[Speaker 2] A simple Indian girl on the inside.
[Speaker 2] I'm touched.