[Speaker 1] Let go.
[Speaker 2]- Exactly...let go.
[Speaker 1] Gopu, my fingers have surrounded the fritter from all sides.
[Speaker 2] And, my fingers...
[Speaker 2]...have surrounded your fingers from all sides.
[Speaker 4]Don't be scared, Madhav.
[Speaker 4]Let go, Gopu.
[Speaker 4]Otherwise...I'll turn off the lights.
[Speaker 3]Don't be scared, Gopu.
[Speaker 3]If you turn off the light, I have a candle.
[Lucky]Oh shit
[Speaker 3] Even if we've to go over your dead bodies...
[Speaker 3]...this fritter will be ours.
[Speaker 5]- What is this?
[Speaker 5] You guys are fighting over a fritter.
[Speaker 3] This is not just about one fritter.
[Speaker 3] It's about the sauce too!
[Speaker 1] Let go, Gopu.
[Speaker 2] - Let go. Let go!
[Speaker 3] Oh sh**
[Speaker 4] Gopu.
[Speaker 4] Gopu Ching.
[Speaker 4] I love Desi Chinese...
[Speaker 5] - Laxman... Behave yourself.
[Speaker 4] ...with my fritter.