[Speaker 1] Welcome.
[Speaker 1] Welcome to your dream home.
[Speaker 1] Look.
[Speaker 1] German modular kitchen.
[Speaker 1] Royal mahogany wooden flooring.
[Speaker 1] And handmade artefacts from around the world.
[Speaker 2] All that is fine,
[Speaker 2] but these artefacts have to go.
[Speaker 1] Ma'am, sir, these are rare antique pieces.
[Speaker 2] Yeah, but they look so cheap.
[Speaker 2] Babe, guess the previous owner had no taste at all.
[Speaker 3] Yeah, sweetheart.
[Speaker 3] Not just his taste,
[Speaker 3] his sense of Vaastu was also pretty bad.
[Speaker 3] This door should've been facing southeast instead of southwest.
[Speaker 3] No wonder he went bankrupt.
[Speaker 2] Oh my, God!
[Speaker 1] What happened, ma'am?
[Speaker 2] What happened?
[Speaker 2] Look at the colour of the sofa.
[Speaker 2] Baby, people are right.
[Speaker 2] You can buy a house with money but not taste.
[Speaker 2] Excuse me.
[Speaker 2] This sofa has to go.
[Speaker 2]This has to go.
[Speaker 2] This...has to go.
[Speaker 2] This...definitely has to go.
[Speaker 2] The house is okay.
[Speaker 2] We'll let you know.
[Speaker 3] Baby, I'll be right back.
[Speaker 3] Bro, listen to me.
[Speaker 3] I heard that the previous owner is pretty desperate to sell the place.
[Speaker 3] Because that scum's gone bankrupt.
[Speaker 3] Ohh...
[Speaker 3] Look bro, if you can get me this place at a cheaper rate,
[Speaker 3] I'll give you an extra commission.
[Speaker 3] Five per cent.
[Speaker 1]- Really?
[Speaker 3] Really.
[Speaker 3] Five per cent.
[Speaker 1] Five per cent?
[Speaker 1] Wow!
[Speaker 1] - Hey, nice car, bro.
[Speaker 3] - Yeah.
[Speaker 1] But doesn't the colour look too cheap?
[Speaker 3] Cheap? No.
[Speaker 1] Wait a second.
[Speaker 2] What's he doing?
[Speaker 1] This colour...has to go.