[Speaker 1]Mr. Tripathi.
[Speaker 1] Mr. Tripathi.
[Speaker 1] Relay this.
[Speaker 2] Sure, sir.
[Speaker 2]Skyline 777, we just received information,
[Speaker 2] that Gulf Pacific 747 which couldn't land in Cochin,
[Speaker 2] has safely landed in Trivandrum airport.
[Speaker 2] Visibility is 3000 meters,
[Speaker 2] weather is clear.
[Speaker 3] Copy.
[Speaker 4] Sir, Bengaluru is our planned alternative.
[Speaker 4] And we need approximately 3300 kgs fuel to reach Bengaluru.
[Speaker 4] And currently, we have 3900 kgs fuel.
[Speaker 4] I think we should immediately divert to Bengaluru.
[Speaker 4] It's just safer.
[Speaker 3] Why Bengaluru and not Trivandrum?
[Speaker 3] Quickly.
[Speaker 4] Because the distance between Trivandrum and Cochin
[Speaker 4] is only 127 nautical miles.
[Speaker 4] If Cochin has bad weather,
[Speaker 4] chances are the Trivandrum's weather could be equally bad.
[Speaker 3] Never go to a place where your thought doesn't reach before you.
[Speaker 3] Get Trivandrum's weather report again.
[Speaker 4] Cochin, Skyline 777 requesting Trivandrum weather details.
[Speaker 2] Skyline 777, visibility in Trivandrum is 3000 meters...
[Speaker 2] Clouds at 1500 feet.
[Speaker 2] I repeat, clouds at 1500 feet.
[Speaker 3] Redesignate alternate to Trivandrum.
[Speaker 4] But, sir...
[Speaker 3] Look.
[Speaker 3] If we fly to Trivandrum instead of Bengaluru,
[Speaker 3] then we'll save fuel.
[Speaker 3] With the extra fuel, we can attempt another landing here.
[Speaker 4] I don't have a good feeling about this, sir.
[Speaker 3] At 35000 feet above the ground,
[Speaker 3] calculations count not feelings.